Guide to the Port Authority of Allegheny County, Press Releases, 1977-1985 AIS.2017.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Port Authority of Allegheny County, Press Releases
1977-1985
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Port Authority of Allegheny County
AIS.2017.10
0.42 Linear Feet (1 box)
Includes press releases from the Port Authority of Allegheny County, the Pittsburgh area's public transportation system.
History
The Port Authority of Allegheny County was created in 1956 by the Pennsylvania State Legislature; in 1959 the legislature allowed the Authority to purchase and consolidate privately-owned trasportation companies that were providing transportation services throughout Allegheny County. The companies were officially acquired in 1963 and the Port Authority began service in March 1964.
Scope and Content Notes
Press releases from the Port Authority of Allegheny County that detail the operational and administrative changes the organization went through from 1977 until 1985. Folders consist of press releases detailing construction projects, peronnel changes, system-wide changes and innovations, and other notices regarding the Port Authority's transit services and leadership.
Previous Citation
Port Authority of Allegheny County, Press Releases, 1977-1985, AIS.2017.10, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
MPamC
Local transit -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Press releases; Port Authority of Allegheny County
- Press releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Press releases, March-April 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Press releases, August 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Press releases, September-October 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Press releases, November-December 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Press releases, January-February 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Press releases, March 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Press releases, April 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Press releases, May-September 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Press releases, October-December 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Press releases, January-May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Press releases, September-October 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Press releases, February-April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Press releases, May-July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Press releases, August-October 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Press releases, November-December 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Press releases, January-February 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Press releases, April-May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Press releases, June-July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Press releases, September-November 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Press releases, January-February 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Press releases, March-April 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Press releases, May-June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Press releases, July-October 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Press releases, November-December 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Press releases, January-March 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Press releases, April-May 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Press releases, June-December 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Press releases, February-May 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Press releases, June 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Press releases, July-August 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Press releases, September 1985-January 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Press releases, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)